https://surbitonchurch.org.uk/cookies-privacy/

Cookies & Privacy
Home > About us  > Our Policies > Cookies & Privacy
INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE SITE
Some personal data is collected through the site when you voluntarily choose to provide us with personal data.
The Contact Form – The information collected via the form simply allows us to reply to you/answer any questions, etc.
SHARING AND USAGE ON COLLECTED INFORMATION
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
USE OF COOKIES
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit.
To learn more about cookies, you can visit www.aboutcookies.org. You will also find details on how to block and delete cookies from your computer as well as more general information about cookies. For information on how to do this on the browser of your mobile phone you will need to refer to your handset manual.
THE COOKIES WE USE
Google Analytics – These cookies collect information about how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don’t collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.
This data helps us to understand:
Which pages people visit on the site
Which internet browsers are being used
What is popular on the site
Which interactive tools are used by visitors
You can find out more about Google’s cookies on their privacy policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also install the Google Analytics Opt-out tools in your browser: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
By using our website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.
YouTube & Vimeo – If you play an embedded video on our site, there may a cookie set by YouTube or Vimeo containing anonymous, non personally-identifiable information about the number of playbacks of embedded videos. To find out more please visit YouTube’s embedding videos information page. You can find out more on the Google Privacy Policy (Google owns YouTube):http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ and the Vimeo Privacy Policy: http://vimeo.com/privacy
Sharing Tools – If you use one of the ‘Share’ buttons, an anonymous cookie may be set by addthis.com to help you to easily bookmark/share selected pages through a number of popular social networks. They also help us know what pages are being bookmarked/shared. You can find out more on the AddThis Privacy Policy: http://www.addthis.com/privacy
If you ‘Like’ or ‘Tweet’ using these services, third party websites may set a cookie when you are also logged in to their service (like Facebook or Twitter). We do not control these cookies and you should check the relevant third party website for more information about these cookies.
NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the this website.
EXTERNAL LINKS
We are not responsible for the availability or content of external sites that may be linked to, from the site. If you find a broken link or if you have any questions or concerns about a link, please contact us.
Search for:
